[{"answer": " Hi, guys.  Thanks for coming to book club tonight.  Grab your drink and som", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Hi, guys.  Thanks for coming to book club tonight.  Grab your drink and som", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " This salad is so delicious.  Did you make it, Tommy", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 16, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " I did.  Its pretty simple.  Ill give you the recipe later", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 17, "question": " This salad is so delicious.  Did you make it, Tommy", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Thanks", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 18, "question": " I did.  Its pretty simple.  Ill give you the recipe later", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " So, did anyone bring any discussion questions about our book tonight", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Thanks", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " I have a few.  Do you think the plot of the book was predictable", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 20, "question": " So, did anyone bring any discussion questions about our book tonight", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " I dont think so.  I thought the story was pretty suspenseful.  I didnt know wha", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 21, "question": " I have a few.  Do you think the plot of the book was predictable", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " I agree.  The twist at the end totally surprised me too", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 25, "question": " I dont think so.  I thought the story was pretty suspenseful.  I didnt know wha", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Yeah, this book was a page-turner.  I usually read for a while before I go t", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 29, "question": " I agree.  The twist at the end totally surprised me too", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " I know.  It was hard to put down.  So, heres another question.  If you were th", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Yeah, this book was a page-turner.  I usually read for a while before I go t", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " I hate to admit it, but I didnt read the book this time.  I only read about 5", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I know.  It was hard to put down.  So, heres another question.  If you were th", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " You didnt read it?  Shame.  Then we wont tell you.  Just kidding.  Well, you kno", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 43, "question": " I hate to admit it, but I didnt read the book this time.  I only read about 5", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Oh, OK", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 48, "question": " You didnt read it?  Shame.  Then we wont tell you.  Just kidding.  Well, you kno", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Its kind of hard for me to imagine, but if I were her, I might have done th", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Oh, OK", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " But dont you think that murdering him was wrong?  I mean, she could hav", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Its kind of hard for me to imagine, but if I were her, I might have done th", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " I guess, but I think she felt that divorce wasnt an option for her.  He woul", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 57, "question": " But dont you think that murdering him was wrong?  I mean, she could hav", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Maybe youre right.  Ive heard of abused women doing similar things to wha", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 61, "question": " I guess, but I think she felt that divorce wasnt an option for her.  He woul", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": "   Me too.  Its hard to imagine ourselves in her shoes, but we might have don", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Maybe youre right.  Ive heard of abused women doing similar things to wha", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " I liked it a lot.  I thought it was very well written.  Ive read some books by th", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 69, "question": "   Me too.  Its hard to imagine ourselves in her shoes, but we might have don", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " I thought the beginning was a bit boring.  Thats one of the reasons why I didn", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 73, "question": " I liked it a lot.  I thought it was very well written.  Ive read some books by th", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " What was wrong with the kids", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 77, "question": " I thought the beginning was a bit boring.  Thats one of the reasons why I didn", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Well, one got sick with the flu for two weeks and then when they got better, th", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 78, "question": " What was wrong with the kids", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Thats too bad.  Are they feeling better now", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Well, one got sick with the flu for two weeks and then when they got better, th", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yes, thank goodness.  Theyre both back at school", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Thats too bad.  Are they feeling better now", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK, back to the book.  Any other comments on if you liked it", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Yes, thank goodness.  Theyre both back at school", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " I agree with you, Tommy.  I liked the book a lot.  I thought the story was reall", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 89, "question": " OK, back to the book.  Any other comments on if you liked it", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Me too.  I would definitely recommend it to other people.  Tracey, if you ha", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 93, "question": " I agree with you, Tommy.  I liked the book a lot.  I thought the story was reall", "qSentId": 92},{"answer": " Maybe Ill try to read the rest this month.  It must get better if you all think it", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 97, "question": " Me too.  I would definitely recommend it to other people.  Tracey, if you ha", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " You should try.  It really is a good book", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Maybe Ill try to read the rest this month.  It must get better if you all think it", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " So, do you guys want to pick our next book tonight", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 102, "question": " You should try.  It really is a good book", "qSentId": 101},{"answer": " Yeah, lets do that now", "docId": "10-03", "aSentId": 103, "question": " So, do you guys want to pick our next book tonight", "qSentId": 102}]
